AoM Records 5593
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Series I. ADMINISTRATIVE RECORDS
  - Sub-Series B. ANNUAL MEETINGS
    - Annual Meeting, Proceedings, San Francisco, "Research Toward the Development of Management Thought." Addresses, 1966 (Box 15, Folder 16)
      decision making, org. change, administration in academia, psychology and leadership, forecasting-output scheduling, risk taking, simulation
    - Annual Meeting, San Francisco, 1966 (Box 15, Folder 17)
      includes Annual Committee Reports
    - Annual Meetings, San Francisco, Reports and Attendee List, 1966 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Annual Meetings, San Francisco, Financial Records, 1966 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Annual Meeting, San Francisco, 1966 (Box 16, Folder 3)
      includes correspondence of Robert Henderson, Secretary-Treasurer in 1966
    - Annual Meeting, San Francisco, 1966 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Annual Meeting, Proceedings, Washington, D.C., Promising research directions. Addresses, 1967 (Box 16, Folder 5)
      Macrosociology (Etzioni), management socio- industrial complex, empiricism in international management, org. theory, inter-departmental deal making, managerial climate-O.B., organizational change, power-deal making, minorities goals in complex organization
    - Annual Meeting, Proceedings, Washington, D.C., 1967 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Annual Meeting, Proceedings, Washington, D.C., 1967 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Annual Meeting, Proceedings, Washington, D.C., 1967 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Annual Meeting, Proceedings, Cincinnati, OH, 1968 (Box 16, Folder 9)
      Organizational Structure and Behavior, Lorsch, Gordon, Cummings, Lazurus, Glueck, Lawrence. Technology, creativity, organizational change, minorities, group risk taking, organizational diversity, integrations-information system, manager motivation, corpor
    - Annual Meeting, Proceedings, Cincinnati, OH, 1968 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Annual Meeting, Proceedings, Cincinnati, OH, 1968 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Annual Meeting, Proceedings, Cincinnati, OH, 1968 (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - Annual Meeting, Cincinnati, OR, 1968 (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - 29th Annual Meeting, Reports, 1968 (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - 29th Annual Meeting, Cincinnati, 1968-1969 (Box 16, Folder 15)
      Program
    - Annual Meeting, Proceedings, Chicago, 1969 (Box 17, Folder 1)
      Managing Complex Organizations. Paul J. Gordon, Farmer, Belasco. Management Complex org, multi-industrial corporations, conglomerates, management theory v. practice, Markov chain, TIO, staff v. line, leadership, satisfaction, personality, normative theory
    - Annual Meeting, Proceedings, Chicago, 1969 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Annual Meeting, Chicago, 1969 (Box 17, Folder 3-14)
    - Annual Meeting, San Diego, CA, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 15-16)
    - Annual Meeting, 1970 (Box 18, Folder 1)
      includes minutes of Annual Meeting, San Diego
    - 30th Annual Meeting, San Diego, Correspondence, 1970 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Annual Meeting, San Diego, 1970 (Box 18, Folder 3)
      Agenda, Program and Attendance List
    - Annual Meeting, 1970 (Box 18, Folder 4)
      includes Proceedings, San Diego, CA
    - Annual Meeting, San Diego, CA, 1970 (Box 18, Folder 5-14)
    - Annual Meeting, Proceedings, Atlanta, GA, Presidential address - W. Wolf. Addresses, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 15)
      contemporary systems of management, deal making, strategy and structures. Research: Methodology: research sites, design, unobtrusive measures, validity, field work, executive performance; teaching management-management international business, O.D., motiva
    - Annual Meeting, Proceedings, Atlanta, GA, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - Annual Meeting, Proceedings, Atlanta, GA, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - Annual Meeting, Atlanta, GA, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - Annual Meeting, Atlanta, GA, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 1-4)
    - Annual Meeting, Atlanta, GA, Correspondence, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Annual Meeting, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 6)
      includes information concerning the role of the newly established professional division in the program of the annual meeting, Atlanta, GA
    - Annual Meeting, Atlanta, GA, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Annual Meeting, Minutes, Atlanta, GA, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Annual Meeting, Minneapolis, MN, 1972 (Box 19, Folder 9-12)
    - 32nd Annual Meeting, Minneapolis, MN, Program and Agenda, 1972 (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - Annual Meeting, Minneapolis, MN, 1972 (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - Annual Meeting, Proceedings, Minneapolis, MN, Presidential address, 1972 (Box 19, Folder 15)
      George A. Steiner, Action Oriented Research. Divisions: O.D./organizational and management theory, business policy and planning division, management consulting division, productions/op. management history, O.B., manpower, social issues, management educati
    - Annual Meeting, Minneapolis, MN, Condensed Program, 1972 (Box 19, Folder 16)
      August 13 - 16, 1972
    - Annual Meeting, Proceedings, Minneapolis, MN, 1972 (Box 19, Folder 17)
    - Annual Meeting, Boston, MA, 1973 (Box 19, Folder 18-19)
    - Annual Meeting, Boston, MA, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 1-9)
    - Annual Meeting, Proceedings, Boston, MA, Divisions, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 10)
      current issues: O Design, energy, forecasts for academics
    - Annual Meeting, Seattle, WA, 1974 (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - Annual Meeting, Seattle, WA, 1974 (Box 20, Folder 12)
      Div. Business policy, international management, management consulting, management education and development history, manpower, O.B., O.D., organization and management theory, organizational communications, production operation management, social issues
    - Annual Meeting, Seattle, WA, 1974 (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - Annual Meeting, Seattle, WA, 1974 (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - Annual Meeting, Seattle, WA, 1974 (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - Annual Meeting, Proceedings, New Orleans, LA, Divisions, 1975 (Box 21, Folder 1)
      history, management education, business policy and planning, production- operations management consultation division, OB, organizational management theory, manpower, international management, social issues, organizational development, organizational commun
    - Annual Meeting, Proceedings, New Orleans, LA, 1975 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Annual Meeting, New Orleans, LA, 1975 (Box 21, Folder 3-5)
    - Annual Meeting, Preliminary Program, New Orleans, LA, 1975 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Annual Meeting, New Orleans, LA, 1975 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Annual Meeting (36th), Kansas City, MO, 1976 (Box 22, Folder 1)
      Preliminary Program, August 11 - 14, 1976
    - Annual Meeting (36th), Kansas City, MO, 1976 (Box 22, Folder 2)
      Program and Agenda, August 1976
    - Annual Meeting, Proceedings, Kansas City, MO, 1976 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Annual Meeting, Proceedings, Kansas City, MO, 1976 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Annual Meeting, Kansas City, MO, 1976 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Annual Meeting, Kissimmee, FL, Correspondence and Reports, 1977 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Annual Meeting, 1977 (Box 23, Folder 1)
      Correspondence RE: The Program for the 1978 Meeting
    - Annual Meeting (37th), Kissimmee, FL, 1977 (Box 23, Folder 2)
      August 14-17, 1977
    - Annual Meeting, Final Program, Kissimmee, FL, 1977 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Annual Meeting, Preliminary Program, San Francisco, CA, 1978 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Annual Meeting, Final Program, San Francisco, CA, 1978 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Annual Meeting, San Francisco, CA, 1978 (Box 23, Folder 6)
      Correspondence and Reports, August 9 - 13, 1978
    - Annual Meeting, Preliminary Program, Atlanta, GA, 1979 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Annual Meeting, Atlanta, GA, Meeting of Women's Support Network, 1979 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Academy of Management Annual Meeting, Atlanta, GA, Preliminary Program, 1979 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Academy of Management Annual Meeting, Atlanta, GA, Final Program, 1979 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Annual Meeting (40th), Detroit, MI, Final Program, 1980 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Annual Meeting (40th), Proceedings, Detroit, MI, 1980 (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Annual Meeting (40th), Detroit, MI, Preliminary, 1980 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Annual Meeting (41st), San Diego, CA, Final Program, 1981 (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Annual Meeting (42nd), New York City, Program, 1982 (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Annual Meeting, General (Box 24, Folder 10)
      Includes list of locations of annual meetings, policies concerning meetings, etc.
    - Annual Meeting, Program, Dallas, TX, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Annual Meeting, Program, Boston, MA, 1984 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Annual Meeting, Program, San Diego, CA, 1985 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Annual Meeting, Program, Chicago, IL, 1986 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Annual Meeting, Program, New Orleans, LA, 1987 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Sub-Series C. Executive Officers
    Alphabetical Order
    - Bedeian, A., 1974 (Box 26, Folder 1)
      Correspondence
    - Bedeian, A., 1975-1976 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Bedeian, A., 1979-1980 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Bedeian, A., 1980 (Box 26, Folder 4-6)
    - Bedeian, A., 1981 (Box 26, Folder 7-8)
    - Bedeian, A., 1981-1985 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Bedeian, A., 1979 (Box 27, Folder 1-11)
      Academy Meeting
    - Bedeian, A. (Box 27, Folder 1-9)
      Academy Archives
    - Bedeian, A. (Box 27, Folder 12)
      CIOS
    - Bedeian, A., 1979 (Box 27, Folder 13)
      Miscellaneous
    - Brown, Alvin, 1956-1957 (Box 27, Folder 14)
    - Coffey, Bob, Secretary-Treasurer, 1973 (Box 28, Folder 1)
      Executive Officer's File
    - Coffey, Bob, Secretary-Treasurer, 1973 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Cummins, L. L., 1974 (Box 28, Folder 3)
      General Correspondence and Materials
    - Cummins, L. L., 1975 (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Cummins, L. L., 1976 (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Cummins, L. L., 1977 (Box 28, Folder 6)
      General Correspondence
    - Cummins, L. L., 1977 (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - Cummins, L. L., Executive Officer, 1978 (Box 28, Folder 8)
      Correspondence with Rosemary Pledger
    - Cummins, L. L., Executive Officer, 1978 (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - Cummins, L. L., 1978 (Box 28, Folder 10)
      Bio
    - Cummins, L. L., Executive Officer, VP Academy of Management, 1978 (Box 28, Folder 11)
    - Cummins, L. L., 1979 (Box 28, Folder 12)
      General Correspondence, Board of Governors
    - Cummins, L. L., 1979 (Box 28, Folder 13)
    - Cummins, L. L., 1979 (Box 28, Folder 14)
      Executive Officer's File, Vice President, Correspondence RE: Thank you for contributions 79 convention
    - Cummins, L. L., President Elect, 1980 (Box 28, Folder 15)
      Executive Officer's Files, January 1980 - August 1980
    - Cummins, L. L., President, 1980 (Box 28, Folder 16)
      Executive Officer's Files, August - September 1980
    - Cummins, L. L., President, 1980 (Box 28, Folder 17)
      Executive Officer's Files, October
    - Cummins, L. L., 1980 (Box 28, Folder 18)
      Board of Governors Meeting, Correspondence and Materials, November - December, 1980
    - Cummins, L. L., President, 1980 (Box 29, Folder 1)
      Correspondence RE: Detroit Meeting
    - Cummins, L. L., President, 1980 (Box 29, Folder 2)
      Correspondence RE: Proceedings
    - Cummins, L. L., President, 1980 (Box 29, Folder 3)
      Correspondence with Glueck
    - Cummins, L. L., 1980 (Box 29, Folder 4)
      General Correspondence RE: Board of Governors
    - Cummins, L. L., President, 1980 (Box 29, Folder 5)
      Material RE: Meeting in Las Vegas
    - Cummins, L. L., President-Elect, 1980 (Box 29, Folder 6)
      Executive Officer Files, (ICS - International Committee on Sci. Management)
    - Cummins, L. L., President-Elect, 1980 (Box 29, Folder 7)
      Executive Officers, Academy of Management Membership Survey
    - Cummins, L. L., President, 1980 (Box 29, Folder 8)
      Executive Officer's File, Correspondence
    - Cummins, L. L., President-Elect, 1980 (Box 29, Folder 9)
      Executive Officer's File, Correspondence RE: Service Recognition
    - Cummins, L. L., President, 1981 (Box 29, Folder 10)
      Resume
    - Cummins, L. L., President, 1980 (Box 29, Folder 11)
      Correspondence and Materials Pertaining to Board of Governors Meeting, August 1980
    - Cummins, L. L., President, 1981 (Box 29, Folder 12)
      Correspondence with New Fellows
    - Cummins, L. L., President, 1981 (Box 29, Folder 13)
      Executive Officer's File, Correspondence RE: Board of Governors Meeting, April/May, 1981
    - Cummins, L. L., 1981 (Box 29, Folder 14)
      Miscellaneous, Business Meeting
    - Cummins, L. L., President, 1981 (Box 29, Folder 15)
      Executive Officer's File, November - January 1981
    - Cummins, L. L., President, 1981 (Box 29, Folder 16)
      Executive Officer's Files, February 1981
    - Cummins, L. L., President, 1981 (Box 29, Folder 17)
      Executive Officer's Files, March - May 1981
    - Cummins, L. L., President, 1981 (Box 29, Folder 18)
      Executive Officer's Files, June - August 1981
    - Cummins, L. L., Past President, 1981 (Box 29, Folder 19)
      Executive Officer's Files, August 1981
    - Dale, Ernest, President-Elect, 1967 (Box 29, Folder 20)
      Executive Officer's Files
    - Dale, Ernest, President, 1968 (Box 29, Folder 21-22)
    - Davis, Keith, President, 1956-1985 (Box 30, Folder 1-9)
      Correspondence, General
    - Davis, Keith (Box 31, Folder 1)
      Articles
    - Davis, Keith (Box 31, Folder 2)
      Bibliographies
    - Davis, Keith (Box 31, Folder 3-7)
      Books (Correspondence about books authored by Davis)
    - Davis, Keith (Box 32, Folder 1-2)
    - Davis, Keith (Box 32, Folder 3-8)
      Consulting/Speeches, 1940's - 1980's
    - Davis, Keith (Box 32, Folder 9)
      Employment Offers, Etc.
    - Davis, Keith, 1968-1980 (Box 32, Folder 10)
      Fellows (Correspondence)
    - Davis, Keith, 1984 (Box 32, Folder 11)
      50th Anniversary of Academy
    - Davis, Keith (Box 33, Folder 1-3)
      Foreign
    - Davis, Keith (Box 33, Folder 4)
      Institute for Administrative Research
    - Davis, Keith (Box 33, Folder 5)
      International Academy of Management
    - Davis, Keith (Box 33, Folder 6)
      Membership Committee
    - Davis, Keith (Box 33, Folder 7)
      Mountain-Plains Conference
    - Davis, Keith (Box 33, Folder 8)
      Organizational Behavior Division
    - Davis, Keith, 1953 (Box 33, Folder 9)
      Personnel Psychology, Correspondence RE: '53 Article
    - Davis, Keith (Box 33, Folder 10)
      Publications (Academy)
    - Davis, Keith (Box 33, Folder 11)
      Publications-Committee
    - Davis, Keith (Box 33, Folder 12-13)
      Sigma Iota Epsilon (Student Division, Academy of Management)
    - Davis, Keith (Box 34, Folder 1-2)
      Sigma--(cont.)
    - Davis, Keith, 1972-1977 (Box 34, Folder 3-4)
      Social Issues Division
    - Davis, Keith (Box 34, Folder 5)
      Southern Division
    - Davis, Keith (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Davis, Keith (Box 34, Folder 7)
      Western Division
    - Davis, Keith (Box 34, Folder 8)
      Photos, Awards, Interview (2, VHS Tapes) (LP record and oversized certificate placed in map case, drawer #5)
    - Davis, Ralph, President, 1942-1947 (Box 34A, Folder 1)
    - Davis, Ralph, President, 1948 (Box 34A, Folder 2-3)
    - Davis, Ralph, President (Box 34A, Folder 4)
      1950s
    - Davis, Ralph, President (Box 34A, Folder 5)
      1960s
    - Davis, Ralph, President (Box 34A, Folder 6)
      1970s
    - Davis, Ralph, Fellows Group Correspondence (Box 34A, Folder 7-10)
    - Davis, Ralph, International Academy of Management Correspondence (Box 34A, Folder 11)
    - Glueck, William, 1975-1976 (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - Glueck, William, 1977 (Box 35, Folder 2)
      Executive Officer's File, Chairman-Proceedings Ed. for Selection Committee and Other Correspondence
    - Glueck, William, Vice President, 1978 (Box 35, Folder 3)
      Executive Officer's File, Report of Program Schedule Procedures
    - Glueck, William, 1978 (Box 35, Folder 4)
      Executive Officer's File, Correspondence RE: Proceedings Editor
    - Glueck, William, Vice President, 1978 (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - Glueck, William, President-Elect, 1978 (Box 35, Folder 6)
      Executive Officer's Files, Correspondence RE: Task Force Report
    - Glueck, William, Vice President, 1978-1979 (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - Glueck, William, 1979 (Box 35, Folder 8)
      Executive Officer's Files, Correspondence RE: Board of Governors
    - Glueck, William, 1979 (Box 35, Folder 9)
      Executive Officer's Files, Election Material, etc.
    - Glueck, William, President-Elect, 1979 (Box 35, Folder 10)
      Executive Officer's Files, Correspondence RE: Responses to Task Force Report
    - Glueck, William, 1979 (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - Glueck, William, Vice President, 1979 (Box 36, Folder 2)
      Executive Officer's Files, RE: Draft of Task Force Report
    - Glueck, William, President-Elect, 1979 (Box 36, Folder 3)
      Executive Officer's Files, Curriculum Exchange Program
    - Glueck, William, 1979 (Box 36, Folder 4)
      Executive Officer's Files, Tentative Agenda, Business Meeting
    - Glueck, William, 1980 (Box 36, Folder 5)
      Executive Officer's Files, Correspondence, Tape of Luncheon and Transcript of Memorial Service for President Glueck, William
    - Glueck, William, President, 1980 (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - Glueck, William, President, 1980 (Box 36, Folder 7)
      Executive Officer's Files, Correspondence on Division of Research on Women and Ministry
    - Glueck, William, President, 1980 (Box 36, Folder 8)
      Correspondence RE: Newsletter
    - Glueck, William, President, 1980 (Box 36, Folder 9)
      Correspondence on his Death
    - Glueck, William, President, 1980-1981 (Box 36, Folder 10)
      Correspondence RE: Presidential Visits
    - Glueck, William, President ACM, 1980-1981 (Box 36, Folder 11)
      Executive Officer's Files, The Conference Board Correspondence
    - Glueck, William, President AOM, 1980-1981 (Box 36, Folder 12)
    - Goetz, Billy, Secretary-Treasurer, 1956 (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - Goetz, Billy, President, 1958 (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - Gordon, Paul J., 1956 (Box 37, Folder 3)
      Paper, Objectives for Education in Administration reprinted from Hospital Administration, Winter
    - Gordon, Paul J., Vice President, 1967 (Box 37, Folder 4-6)
    - Gordon, Paul J., President-Elect, 1968 (Box 37, Folder 7-9)
    - Gordon, Paul J., President-Elect, 1968 (Box 37, Folder 10)
      Executive Officer's Files, RE: Long Range Planning
    - Gordon, Paul J., President-Elect, 1968 (Box 37, Folder 11)
      Executive Officer's Files, RE: 1967 Questionnaire
    - Gordon, Paul J., 1969 (Box 37, Folder 12)
      Executive Officer's Files, Presidential Newsletter #1, February 18, 1969
    - Gordon, Paul J., 1969 (Box 37, Folder 13)
      Executive Officer's Files, Presidential Newsletter #1
    - Gordon, Paul J., President, 1969 (Box 37, Folder 14-26)
    - Gordon, Paul J., 1976 (Box 37, Folder 27)
    - Henderson, Robert, Secretary-Treasurer, 1966 (Box 38, Folder 1-9)
    - Henderson, Robert, Secretary-Treasurer, 1967 (Box 38, Folder 10-15)
    - Hicks, Herbert, Secretary-Treasurer, 1961-1971 (Box 38, Folder 16)
    - Hicks, Herbert, Associate Secretary-Treasurer, 1971 (Box 38, Folder 17)
    - Hicks, Herbert, Secretary-Treasurer, 1971 (Box 38, Folder 18)
    - Hicks, Herbert, Secretary-Treasurer, 1972 (Box 39, Folder 1-6)
    - Hicks, Herbert, President-Elect, 1973 (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - Hicks, Herbert, President, 1974 (Box 39, Folder 8-10)
    - Hicks, Herbert, President, 1975 (Box 39, Folder 11-14)
    - Hicks, Herbert, President, 1975-1977 (Box 39, Folder 15)
    - Jamison, Charles, 1936 (Box 39a, Folder 1)
    - Jamison, Charles, 1937 (Box 39a, Folder 2)
    - Jamison, Charles, 1938 (Box 39a, Folder 3)
    - Jamison, Charles, 1939 (Box 39a, Folder 4)
    - Jamison, Charles, 1940 (Box 39a, Folder 5)
    - Jamison, Charles, 1941-1942 (Box 39a, Folder 6)
    - Jamison, Charles, 1945-1947 (Box 39a, Folder 7)
    - Jamison, Charles, 1948 (Box 39a, Folder 8)
    - Jamison, Charles, 1949-1955 (Box 39a, Folder 9)
    - Kast, Fremont, President-Elect, Western Division, 1970-1971 (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - Kast, Fremont, As Chairman of Committee to Investigate Relationship Between the Regional Division and the Academy of Management, 1972 (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - Kast, Fremont, Vice President and Program Chair, 1974 (Box 40, Folder 3)
      Executive Officer's File, Correspondence RE: Program Committee
    - Kast, Fremont, Vice President and Program Chair, 1974-1975 (Box 40, Folder 4)
      Executive Officer's File, Correspondence RE: Local Arrangements
    - Kast, Fremont, Vice President and Program Chair, 1974-1975 (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - Kast, Fremont, Vice President, 1974-1975 (Box 40, Folder 6)
      Executive Officer's File, Letters from Robert Coffey
    - Kast, Fremont, President-Elect, 1974-1975 (Box 40, Folder 7)
      Executive Officer's File, Correspondence with Stan Vance
    - Kast, Fremont, Vice President and Program Chair, 1974-1975 (Box 40, Folder 8)
      Executive Officer's File, Correspondence with Herb Hicks
    - Kast, Fremont, 1974-1976 (Box 40, Folder 9)
      Executive Officer's File, Miscellaneous Correspondence
    - Kast, Fremont, 1974-1978 (Box 40, Folder 10)
      Correspondence RE: The Management Education and Development Division
    - Kast, Fremont, Vice President and Program Chair, 1975 (Box 40, Folder 11)
      Correspondence RE: 1975 Annual Meeting General Sessions
    - Kast, Fremont, Vice President and Program Chair, 1975 (Box 40, Folder 12)
      Executive Officer's File, Correspondence RE: Constitutional Amendments
    - Kast, Fremont, Vice President, 1975 (Box 40, Folder 13)
      Executive Officer's File, Correspondence with John B. Miner
    - Kast, Fremont, Vice President and Program Chair, 1975 (Box 40, Folder 14)
      Correspondence RE: Proceedings of the Academy
    - Kast, Fremont, 1975 (Box 40, Folder 15)
    - Kast, Fremont, President-Elect, 1975-1976 (Box 41, Folder 1)
      Executive Officer's File, Lists and Correspondence: Professional Divisions
    - Kast, Fremont, President-Elect, 1975-1976 (Box 41, Folder 2)
      Correspondence: Professional Division Chairpersons
    - Kast, Fremont, President-Elect, 1975-1976 (Box 41, Folder 3)
      Executive Officer's File, Professional Division Policy Committee
    - Kast, Fremont, President-Elect, 1975-1976 (Box 41, Folder 4)
      Executive Officer's File, Correspondence: Proposal for Division Status from Public Sector Interest Group
    - Kast, Fremont, 1975-1977 (Box 41, Folder 5)
      Correspondence RE: International Management Division
    - Kast, Fremont, 1975-1979 (Box 41, Folder 6)
      Correspondence RE: Organization and Management Theory Division Newsletter
    - Kast, Fremont, President, 1976 (Box 41, Folder 7)
      Executive Officer's File, Address to Southern Management Association, November 1976
    - Kast, Fremont, President, 1976 (Box 41, Folder 8)
      Executive Officer's File, Correspondence RE: Professional Division Policy Committee Meeting, Atlanta, GA, November 19, 1976
    - Kast, Fremont, President, 1976 (Box 41, Folder 9)
      Executive Officer's File, Correspondence RE: Board Meeting in Atlanta, November 20, 1976
    - Kast, Fremont, President-Elect, 1976 (Box 41, Folder 10)
      Executive Officer's File, Presidential Luncheon Attendance List and Speech
    - Kast, Fremont, 1976-1977 (Box 41, Folder 11)
      Executive Officer's File, General Correspondence as President
    - Kast, Fremont, 1976-1977 (Box 41, Folder 12)
    - Kast, Fremont, 1976-1977 (Box 41, Folder 13)
    - Kast, Fremont, President, 1976-1977 (Box 41, Folder 14)
      Executive Officer's File, Speeches
    - Kast, Fremont, 1976-1977 (Box 42, Folder 1)
      Executive Officer's File, Presidential Budget and Expenditures